["Here We Go" by Extreme Music playing]
[woman 1] I've known Justin
for four years now,
and he's one of my best friends.
Justin is definitely a bachelor,
but I think that he would be
a great boyfriend.
I know he wants to settle down.
[woman 2] Justin wants somebody
to meet his fire,
but there's some sort of inner turmoil
that he's fighting with, like,
who he's supposed to be with
versus who he wants to be with.
♪ So here we go... ♪
[woman 3] I do believe there's a woman
out there for Justin.
I just feel like he hasn't met his match.
I want Justin to find love
and his place in this world.
♪ Everybody in the shadows
Coming out today ♪
♪ Everybody in the shadows coming out
Here we go... ♪
[man] Justin is one of the most
real people I know,
but he goes for party girls.
He just needs to find
an amazingly sincere woman.
Like, Justin is an amazingly sincere man.
♪ Here we go ♪
[music stops]
[Barbara] Hello!
-Barbara.
-Justin?
-How are you?
-Oh, good. How are you?
-Nice to meet you. [laughs]
-[laughs]
-So nice to meet you.
-You look so pretty.
Thank you so much.
-Is this your first blind date?
-It is my first blind date. I have never--
I was hoping
that you could walk me through this.
[laughs] Oh, gosh! Yeah.
I have no idea where we're going.
If not, we can both say
that this is our first blind date,
and then it started on Bourbon Street.
-Perfect!
-Like, really...
I don't think that you can go
any higher than that,
or any more extreme than that,
to be honest with you.
Oh, this is cute.
It's a good vibe. Thank you.
So, how are you today?
-Blessed and highly favored.
-Yeah?
How are you?
[Justin] I am super excited.
I mean, blind dates are, like,
one of those things that...
just, like, things can either go
super right or super wrong.
-No. Yeah.
-But yeah,
first impressions, I mean...
You know what I'm saying?
I'm Justin.
-Hugs? Okay. Hi.
-I go in for hugs.
-Okay.
-My palms get too sweaty
on these first dates.
-My armpits are sweating right now.
-Okay, cool. Noted.
-It's dripping like...
-[chuckles]
Oh. So, where are you from?
-I'm born and raised here.
-Me too!
I'm probably a hundred percent sure
that we have, like, mutual friends.
-I'm pretty sure we have mutual friends--
-You're Filipino though, right?
-No, I'm not. Do I look Filipino?
-No, I'm just kidding you.
-Are you Filipino?
-I am Filipino. [laughs]
Why are you shaking my hand? Like...
-No, 'cause you're doing this.
-You stuck your hand out.
-I'm sorry. All right.
-I'm sorry. I'm bad at dates.
I need a shot of tequila...
and I'll get a cocktail too.
-Let's go!
-Is that too much for a first date?
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know how to flirt.
That's kinda my way of flirting.
"Hey, um, let's take a shot."
You from here?
I'm not. I am from, like a nomad.
-Go ahead.
-Um...
born in Ohio,
moved to San Antonio, Texas,
and moved to Houston,
went to school in Alabama.
-I'm gonna write this down. [laughs]
-I know, right?
Are your parents in Chalmette?
Yeah.
They did the whole Hurricane Katrina thing
and they stayed...
-Okay.
-...and they rebuilt,
and they're in the same house.
'Cause it happened to me
during my senior year in high school.
-Oh, wow. Where did y'all go?
-So, like...
So, we went to Houston.
So, I went from this school
that had, like, 500 students
-to a school which had, like, 5,000 kids.
-[laughs]
That Houston school was pretty rough.
First day, I was eating at a lunch table
like this,
and then all of a sudden, like,
somebody hops over the table,
and this brawl between New Orleans
and Houston happened.
I was like, you know what?
-No.
-I'll take the hurricane!
-Yeah.
-That's... That's... crazy!
Yeah.
-What is it that you do down here?
-I'm a singer.
[Justin] Ooh!
I don't really have residency anywhere.
I just really put on my own shows,
and I travel and do other shows.
-That's amazing!
-Yeah.
I always wanted to be a singer.
You always wanted to sing?
-Yeah. I could never sing though.
-[laughs]
But karaoke, I'm, like, great.
Karaoke I'm okay.
-We might have to try. [laughs]
-Maybe after this...
I'm the photo-lead for an eyewear company
in New Orleans.
-Nice!
-So what do you do?
The main thing that I do, my nine-to-five,
is I work in finance.
It's just so funny
because I'll start by saying,
"Yeah, I'm an accountant."
And they're like,
"Oh, so you're great with math?"
And I'm like, "No!"
And the next thing is, like,
"But you're Asian."
And I'll be, like,
"Also a disappointment."
My mom would love it
if I was an accountant.
-Anyone would love that.
-My mom was super happy
that I went into accounting.
Now, it's, like, "Oh, Justin,
you could have been a doctor.
Why didn't you do that?"
I'm, like, "You told me to do this!
-[laughs]
-This was your idea!"
So, like, around New Orleans,
what are your favorite things to do?
Other than drink?
Yeah, I mean, 'cause I can go on and on
about where I drink, right?
I'm really not here that often
on the weekends.
-I've been, like, full of weddings.
-Too many weddings?
-Yeah!
-You have too many friends.
-I know!
-Weddings are probably
-my favorite things to go to.
-I know.
-Oh, amazing!
-[waiter] Here you go.
[Assata] Yes.
-Oh, my goodness.
-[Assata] Oh, let's get it.
-Cheers.
To first blind dates.
So, what kind of music do you dance to?
Uh, hip-hop.
-Hip-hop? Okay, cool.
-Yeah.
So are you kinda, like,
the break dancing...
Or are you just kinda, like,
the smooth beat vibe?
I mean I feel like
I can get into the smooth vibe...
-Or are you, like...
-...but I can also go into, like... ayyy.
-Okay! [laughs]
-Yeah. [laughs]
-No, we gonna stop that right here.
-[laughs]
This is-- We have had one drink
and we're not starting that!
No more, or you'll be carrying me home.
Period.
-Okay.
-[laughs]
Every time that I get semi drunk,
I'm, like...
-Let's go get a tattoo.
-I'm like, "Let's go get a tattoo."
Then my mom is like, "Justin,
I'm going to cut your skin off
-if you do that."
-[laughs] Aw.
-Let me ask you, how old are you?
-I'm 31.
That sounds about right,
'cause Asians don't raisin.
[both laughing]
-Guess my age.
-Twenty...
-Twenty?
-...eight?
-Twenty eight?
-Thirty?
Oh, I know you did not just--
Thirty! Really?
Twenty...
All right,
this date needs to end right now.
-I'm sorry.
-[scoffs]
-You can see your way out!
-[laughs]
-No.
If I had to guess,
I'd probably say, like, 25.
-Twenty six, actually.
-Oh!
You know you're lying.
You said 20 or 30 at first.
[waiter] Pardon my interruption.
Our table is ready.
-Oh, amazing.
-[bartender] You wanna follow me.
-Sure.
-Cool.
I'll get your chair.
-Thank you.
-After you.
[waiter] Here's a couple of menus.
Thank you.
[waiter]
Are we good with the drinks for now?
Let's do another shot of tequila.
-Yep. Yeah.
-All right, yeah.
I kinda wanna switch to tequila
now that you've been drinking tequila.
-[laughs]
-All right, so you're ready to party.
[laughing]
I might get the chicken liver mousse.
-I've never had liver...
-Chicken liver mousse.
...but I'm down to try it tonight.
Let's do it.
-See, that's how first dates go great.
-[giggles]
Did you grow up lower middle class?
I feel like I grew up
mid to lower middle class.
I don't know.
-So, growing up...
-[laughs] It's always really vague.
...it was more like a community-type thing
where we grew up,
and we kinda, like,
stayed in our little circle.
I could have been an upper-class person,
but, like, according to people
outside of the city,
I was probably broke.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah.
I went to a lot of private schools,
which I was very thankful for,
but we were, like, Payless
and a hand-me-down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I was, like, why does everyone have
this Micheal Kors bag...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
...and this pink Razr phone?
-Why can't I have a pink Razr phone?
-Razr phone! [chuckles]
So, as far as photography goes,
are there certain things
that you wanna photograph?
I'm really into outside, natural lighting.
-Yeah.
-Really flowy, motion blur...
I'm, like, Photoshop queen.
-I can do anything.
-Really?
'Cause I've always wanted
to go to England.
I'll just take a picture of you
out here in New Orleans,
-and Photoshop you in London.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Put me in front of Buckingham Palace.
-That's it.
-Next to the Queen. [laughs]
-Okay, next Instagram post! [laughs]
[laughing]
Something I do to kill time,
I don't know if you are familiar with this
but I like to do mukbangs.
It's, like, you have a shitload of food
in front of you,
and you record yourself eating,
but you're doing it live,
and people are watching you.
For example, I'll have a plate, like,
of 50 chicken wings,
-and I'll just start eating chicken wings.
-[laughs]
That's amazing.
Have you ever done
that hot ramen challenge?
-The two times spicy?
-Yes, I did that on my stream before.
I did that on my stream.
-How did you deal with that? [laughs]
-It was bad. My asshole was burning.
Oh, no, baby! Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
That looks beautiful.
[Assata] It does. It's very colorful.
-All right, so I'm gonna let you try this.
-I'm gonna pray.
-Oh. All right, are you ready?
-Oh, you pray?
-No.
-You trying to pray together?
Ain't nothing gonna make my mama happier
than if we do this.
So, go ahead. Yeah.
Heavenly Father, thank you so much
for this food that we have received.
Thank you for the nourishment.
Thank you for this opportunity.
And bless this food.
In Jesus's name, amen.
[both exhale]
-I feel it, and appreciate that.
-You feel it.
-Well, bon appétit. Let's try this food.
-Yeah, for sure.
-Ooh!
-Go ahead.
[chews loudly] Beau, beau.
[laughs]
It's good. It's flavorful, just like me.
-Yeah. [chuckles]
-Okay.
-Let me take a sip of my water.
-It's deep and flavorful, just like me.
-I can agree with that.
-Thank you. [chuckles]
No, like, I appreciate when a woman
can describe herself,
or describe what she's feeling,
and how she deals with things.
-I appreciate that.
-Aw. Aw!
-Thank you, I appreciate you too.
-Don't cry. Don't cry.
You, pretty much being from here,
-how is your dating life in New Orleans?
-Dating life.
Oh, man, I have tried, I've really tried.
[chuckles] I've given it a valiant effort.
[laughs]
Where are these guys
that I align with in New Orleans?
Where are they?
I'm really struggling to find them.
-Here.
-I'm, like, where are they?
Yeah, really, right there.
I dated a guy for five years,
and then in January,
-I found out that he was cheating on me.
-Mmm.
The universe was, like,
"He doesn't pay all of his bills,"
and I was, "That's okay,
we're gonna figure it out."
The universe kept putting shit
in front of me and I was, like,
"That's fine, we're gonna figure it out."
And then, that happened, and I was,
"Okay,
we're not going to figure that out."
I'm gonna put this baseball bat down,
and I'm gonna tap out of this game.
We're gonna regroup.
-That's wild.
-It was wild.
I've been single
for two and a half years now.
Two and a half years?
I was in a relationship for six years.
-Wow.
-From the time I was 21.
We had this vision
of, like, getting married and having kids,
and then by year six, I was just like,
"I don't know if I can do this."
-That's so tough.
-Yeah.
-I can't even imagine after six years.
-Yeah, yeah.
Do your parents pressure you
in a sense of,
"Oh, when are you gonna get married?"
You know, that type of thing?
You know, It's funny,
that six-year relationship,
like, while that was going on,
my mom was, like,
one of those people that was, like,
-"Justin, you need to save your money."
-[laughs]
Your Filipino mom accent!
"Save your money, Justin.
You don't need to get married yet,"
like, type deal.
-Really? Did she not like your girlfriend?
-I was like, "You don't need to rush."
No, she-- She loved. She loved, loved her.
But I think that as far as Filipinos go,
I think it's more of a financial thing.
I mean, 'cause generally Asian people,
they care more of financial status
-before happiness.
-Mm-hmm.
And when we broke up...
she was just, like,
"I thought you all
were going to get married, Justin."
-[muffled laughter]
-She was so mad.
So, so mad.
Are you like, a Tinder, like, Bumble...
-So, I tried Bumble.
-...dater? Mm-hmm.
I don't always want to be the first one
to say something. I'm like, "Oh, God.
Now I have to say something."
I don't ever--
You have to empathize with...
-Yeah...
-...the guys now, right?
-Yeah. [laughs]
-Whatever! I guess. I guess.
-So, what would your line be?
-So, then I--
Whatever comes up in my brain
at that moment, you know?
-I'm just trying to learn the game.
-I didn't have--
-There-- There is no game.
-Good! [chuckles]
It's just, whatever comes up
in Aunt Bowie's head
is what's coming out of her mouth?
-That's amazing.
-I can just... [imitates app sounds]
Do you get Asian flush?
-No.
-Maybe it's because you're so dark.
[laughs] 'Cause you're so tan.
Being tan is good. I wish I was tan.
Not in the Asian community.
If you're tan, you're broke.
[smacks lips]
Yes, tan skin is looked down upon.
But over here,
I think tan skin is beautiful.
-It is. For me--
-Dark is beautiful.
But then Filipinos naturally
have darker skin, so...
My mom is like, super... M Trng Ngi.
[giggles] How do you know that word?
-[laughs] I, like, dabble in--
-Vietnamese.
You must have a lot of Vietnamese friends.
I do.
-I know a couple of words in Filipino.
-Go ahead.
-Mahal kita.
No, we're not gonna do that
on our first date, girl.
[Lilly laughs]
I love to dance.
-I know, it's so fun!
-It is.
So at a wedding, are you like the--
-The dancer?
-You are?
Oh, hell, yes.
-See what I'm saying?
-Bring the dance party together.
-We'll get along just fine.
-Yeah.
That's why I don't like when there's
too many activities to do at the wedding.
You know, like, the photo booth-- blah.
Take that out.
-DJ!
-Pay--
Oh, see, I'm a band girl.
I've always envisioned,
like, a brass band.
And then, finish it up with the DJ
when everybody's drunk, type deal.
Absolutely.
-That's, like, in my head--
-That's a good way to do it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're down, I'm down to go grab
more drinks if you're up for it?
-Yeah, let's go.
-Yeah? All right. Cool.
-Kill this? Kill it?
-Okay.
-All right, you ready?
-Yeah.
After you.
Thank you.
[Assata] Let's go!
Are you a Leo?
-So, I am a Leo.
-Okay.
-What are you?
-I'm a Scorpio.
And what is the significance of that?
I would say that Scorpios
are usually intellectual.
We definitely love people to be...
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
...honest with us.
We're very sexy, we're mysterious.
So, I feel like... [chuckles]
a hundred percent of our conversation,
I feel like you've confirmed with you
-being a Scorpio then, right?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A hundred percent. So-- So, for me...
I have... uh, always been told
that I am, like, that attention person.
Yeah, you like compliments a lot.
Do I?
-Do I-- Do I ask for them?
-Hmm.
I don't know if I have, like,
a physical type.
Like, I dated skinny band boys for,
like, a long time.
You know, with the bang and everything?
-Yeah.
-Exactly.
And then, like, I dated--
The five-year relationship
was with this broad, tall,
blond farmer boy.
Ooh! What about the short,
dark, Asian guys?
-I've gone on dates with them, for sure.
-Yeah...
-Nothing long term, but I'm into it.
-Yeah.
Have you ever, like, dabbled
in the Asian, uh, cultures?
Is that something
that you've stepped into?
-Of course. Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Of course.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Oh, wow!
-I've always dated introverts.
-Yeah.
-I've never been with an extrovert.
-Why's that?
-I really don't know what it is.
-Do you like being in command
-as far as relationships goes?
-I would say...
I mean, it depends on if we're talking
-in-bed wise submissive--
-Ooh!
Go ahead! Go ahead! We can elaborate.
[stammers] That'd be--
That'd be another time.
So, what next though?
Would you be down to grab drinks
after this?
Usually, I would, but it's a weeknight,
and it's getting a little late.
-I think I should probably head out.
-[laughs] Understandable.
-I think I should catch a Lyft.
-You're gonna catch a Lyft?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Well, before you leave,
would you mind if I got your number?
-Yeah? You want my number?
-Yeah. A hundred percent. Go ahead.
Cool. I'm calling you
just to make sure that this is--
-[chuckles]  My number?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those people--
I did that back in middle school.
-There you are.
-I need confirmation.
No, but I appreciate you coming.
-It's been so nice.
-So nice. Yeah. [smooches]
-So nice meeting you.
-Thank you so much.
-I appreciate you for coming down.
-You too.
-I will talk to you soon.
-We'll talk soon.
-Yeah, for sure.
-Take care.
Yeah. See ya.
[exhales audibly]
Oh...
[soft music playing]
-[Justin] After you.
-[Lilly] Oh.
[Justin] It's fancy here.
[Lilly] And so pretty.
[both laughing]
[Justin] Zero to ten,
how do you rate this as a date?
I'd say it's ten.
The surprise that I had whenever I saw you
was a hundred percent,
like genuinely, I was like,
"Oh, thank you, God!"
-Oh, my Gosh! I'm blushing. [giggles]
-Uh, no, it was super--
I was very attracted to you.
-Thank you so much.
-Girl!
I love how creative you are. Um...
and everything that you're trying to do
with your photography and stuff like that.
-It's super attractive.
-Thank you.
Usually, the first date I go on
with someone,
they end up being my boyfriend
for, like, four years.
I'm not saying you're gonna be
my boyfriend. I don't wanna scare you,
but usually, that one date...
it's like, bam!
Like, okay, we're in love now.
-Oh, Lord!
-Yeah, we're together. [chuckles]
Mahal kita.
Mahal kita! [laughs]
You exceed all types...
-Like, no, for real.
-[laughs] Oh, Justin.
As far as expectations go,
you exceed all expectations.
From the hair, to the-- To the--
To the braces.
-to the dress. Yeah, one hundred percent..
-Oh, thank you. My little brace face.
-Thank you.
-A hundred percent. It works for you.
Thank you.
How about you with Mardi Gras?
-Mardi Gras?
-Go ahead.
Okay, to be honest,
I'm not the biggest Mardi Gras fan.
I've never thrown beads.
I can't say I know what that's like.
[stammers] We're about to throw some beads
right now.
We're about to knock some things off
the bucket list, baby.
-I don't want to hurt anybody.
-Don't hit any cars.
-They're so painful.
-To be honest with you,
I feel like
somebody's going to get pelted.
So what we could do
is we could do something like this.
Or we could do something like this.
-You're so cute. [chuckles]
-Oh.
-Aw.
-I'm about to have a heart attack.
Okay. All right, I can take that. [laughs]
-[laughs]
-You ready to go though?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, let's go.
I've never been, like, out on a date
in the French Quarter.
We're having new experiences.
-We learn new things every day.
-How do you feel about the food?
-I think the food was good.
-Yeah.
-Did you have fun?
You're a very playful person.
Yeah, I feel, like, most people say
that I don't take anything seriously.
[laughs]
"Justin, you need to be more serious."
Well, I don't know. Life's really short.
You don't have to take everything
so seriously.
I feel maybe you took things seriously
for a very long time...
-Mmm.
-...and now you're finally having fun.
Yeah.
Be honest, would you do this again?
Yeah, I mean, it was fun.
You have this personality that...
-I've never encountered.
-[laughs]
What personality is that?
I've never met somebody
that's a hundred percent open as to...
[chuckles]
"This is who I am from the get-go."
-Oh, my goodness! We're here?
-[driver] This is your stop.
-It was amazing meeting you. For sure.
-It was nice to meet you.
-Have a great night.
-Same to you.
-See ya.
-See ya. Have a good one.
[Exhales]
I don't remember the last time I prayed,
but I've also never been more willing
to pray in my life.
-If we're being real.
-Oh.
I hope that no matter what happens,
that you get something
from this encounter with me.
You just never know who God has for you.
I never thought I would go on a date
where I had no idea what the person
was like or what they looked like,
-and actually enjoyed it as much as I did.
-[laughs]
No, I really enjoyed it.
This has been so nice.
Do you plan on having a family
or kids anytime soon?
I am not in any rush to have kids
or get married.
It's definitely all about the right place
and the right time.
I had a good time.
Did you?
-[laughs] Honestly, I did.
-I'm glad.
You're a fun person.
And it was better than what I thought
it was going to be.
I'd love to get your number
before we leave.
Yeah. Absolutely.
But yeah. No...
I'll call you and I appreciate you coming.
All right, text me.
-I will. Will do.
-Give me a call. [giggles]
-All right. Have a good night, bye.
-Same to you.
-Bye.
-I appreciate you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I will let you out this side.
Okay. Thank you.
[grunts, exhales]
["Run With The Sun" by Nick Kingsley
and Hannah Hart playing]
♪ To run with the sun... ♪
-Hi!
-[Justin] How are you?
[Ann] How are you?
Ann, it's good to see you again.
Nice to see you.
So, I have a question.
-Have you ever been to the museum?
-I have not.
Isn't that crazy?
[laughs] That's so bad!
-That's not terrible, I've heard worse.
-I've been to the other ones.
-I just haven't been over here.
-I've heard worse.
-Would you be down for that?
-Yeah. Is that what you want to do?
I have two tickets,
so it's already been planned. [chuckles]
I love your shoes, though.
-Aren't these fun? Thank you.
-I really do.
They're actually Converse.
♪ To run with the sun ♪
♪ Run with the sun ♪